[
  {
    "substring": "Ma",
    "answers": [
      "MG",
      "ML",
      "MO",
      "MH",
      "MK",
      "MU",
      "MT",
      "MW",
      "MV",
      "MR",
      "MY"
    ],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ma'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Sa",
    "answers": ["WS", "SA", "MF", "SH", "KN", "ST", "SM", "LC", "VC"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Sa'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Pa",
    "answers": ["PS", "PW", "PY", "PA", "PG", "PK"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Pa'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Mo",
    "answers": ["ME", "MD", "MA", "MC", "MN", "MZ"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Mo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Be",
    "answers": ["BE", "BM", "BJ", "BY", "BZ"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Be'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Gu",
    "answers": ["GW", "GT", "GY", "GG", "GN"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Gu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "So",
    "answers": ["ZA", "SB", "SO", "SS", "KR"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'So'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ba",
    "answers": ["BD", "BB", "BH", "BS"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ba'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Bo",
    "answers": ["BA", "BO", "BV", "BW"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Bo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Tu",
    "answers": ["TM", "TN", "TV", "TR"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Tu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ca",
    "answers": ["CM", "CA", "CV", "KH"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ca'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Li",
    "answers": ["LI", "LT", "LR", "LY"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Li'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "An",
    "answers": ["AD", "AG", "AO", "AQ"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'An'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Bu",
    "answers": ["BF", "BG", "BI"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Bu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Se",
    "answers": ["RS", "SN", "SC"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Se'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ta",
    "answers": ["TJ", "TZ", "TW"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ta'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Gr",
    "answers": ["GR", "GD", "GL"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Gr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Un",
    "answers": ["GB", "US", "AE"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Un'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ir",
    "answers": ["IQ", "IR", "IE"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ir'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ni",
    "answers": ["NI", "NE", "NG"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ni'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ne",
    "answers": ["NL", "NZ", "NP"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ne'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "No",
    "answers": ["NO", "NF", "KP"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'No'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Co",
    "answers": ["CO", "CR", "KM"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Co'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ch",
    "answers": ["CN", "CL", "TD"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ch'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Al",
    "answers": ["DZ", "AL", "AX"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Al'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ar",
    "answers": ["AM", "AR", "AW"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ar'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Br",
    "answers": ["BN", "BR"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Br'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ja",
    "answers": ["JM", "JP"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ja'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Re",
    "answers": ["RE", "CG"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Re'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ge",
    "answers": ["GE", "DE"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ge'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ga",
    "answers": ["GA", "GM"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ga'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Ho",
    "answers": ["HK", "HN"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Ho'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Po",
    "answers": ["PT", "PL"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Po'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Es",
    "answers": ["EE", "SZ"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Es'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Is",
    "answers": ["IM", "IL"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Is'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Fi",
    "answers": ["FI", "FJ"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Fi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Fa",
    "answers": ["FK", "FO"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Fa'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Na",
    "answers": ["NA", "NR"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Na'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Va",
    "answers": ["VU", "VA"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Va'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Sw",
    "answers": ["CH", "SE"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Sw'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "De",
    "answers": ["CD", "DK"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'De'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Su",
    "answers": ["SR", "SD"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Su'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Sl",
    "answers": ["SK", "SI"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Sl'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Si",
    "answers": ["SL", "SG"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Si'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Do",
    "answers": ["DO", "DM"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Do'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Le",
    "answers": ["LB", "LS"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Le'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "La",
    "answers": ["LA", "LV"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'La'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "To",
    "answers": ["TO", "TG"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'To'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "Au",
    "answers": ["AU", "AT"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'Au'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "In",
    "answers": ["IN", "ID"],
    "question": "Name starts with 'In'"
  },
  { "substring": "Bh", "answers": ["BT"], "question": "Name starts with 'Bh'" },
  { "substring": "Je", "answers": ["JE"], "question": "Name starts with 'Je'" },
  { "substring": "Ru", "answers": ["RU"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ru'" },
  { "substring": "Rw", "answers": ["RW"], "question": "Name starts with 'Rw'" },
  { "substring": "Ro", "answers": ["RO"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ro'" },
  { "substring": "Eq", "answers": ["GQ"], "question": "Name starts with 'Eq'" },
  { "substring": "El", "answers": ["SV"], "question": "Name starts with 'El'" },
  { "substring": "Gh", "answers": ["GH"], "question": "Name starts with 'Gh'" },
  { "substring": "Om", "answers": ["OM"], "question": "Name starts with 'Om'" },
  { "substring": "Jo", "answers": ["JO"], "question": "Name starts with 'Jo'" },
  { "substring": "Cr", "answers": ["HR"], "question": "Name starts with 'Cr'" },
  { "substring": "Ha", "answers": ["HT"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ha'" },
  { "substring": "Hu", "answers": ["HU"], "question": "Name starts with 'Hu'" },
  { "substring": "Ve", "answers": ["VE"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ve'" },
  { "substring": "Pe", "answers": ["PE"], "question": "Name starts with 'Pe'" },
  { "substring": "Ph", "answers": ["PH"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ph'" },
  { "substring": "Za", "answers": ["ZM"], "question": "Name starts with 'Za'" },
  { "substring": "We", "answers": ["EH"], "question": "Name starts with 'We'" },
  { "substring": "Eg", "answers": ["EG"], "question": "Name starts with 'Eg'" },
  { "substring": "Ec", "answers": ["EC"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ec'" },
  { "substring": "It", "answers": ["IT"], "question": "Name starts with 'It'" },
  { "substring": "Vi", "answers": ["VN"], "question": "Name starts with 'Vi'" },
  { "substring": "Et", "answers": ["ET"], "question": "Name starts with 'Et'" },
  { "substring": "Zi", "answers": ["ZW"], "question": "Name starts with 'Zi'" },
  { "substring": "Sp", "answers": ["ES"], "question": "Name starts with 'Sp'" },
  { "substring": "Er", "answers": ["ER"], "question": "Name starts with 'Er'" },
  { "substring": "Uz", "answers": ["UZ"], "question": "Name starts with 'Uz'" },
  { "substring": "My", "answers": ["MM"], "question": "Name starts with 'My'" },
  { "substring": "Ug", "answers": ["UG"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ug'" },
  { "substring": "Me", "answers": ["MX"], "question": "Name starts with 'Me'" },
  { "substring": "Fr", "answers": ["FR"], "question": "Name starts with 'Fr'" },
  { "substring": "Mi", "answers": ["FM"], "question": "Name starts with 'Mi'" },
  { "substring": "Ko", "answers": ["XK"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ko'" },
  { "substring": "Iv", "answers": ["CI"], "question": "Name starts with 'Iv'" },
  { "substring": "Ce", "answers": ["CF"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ce'" },
  { "substring": "Cz", "answers": ["CZ"], "question": "Name starts with 'Cz'" },
  { "substring": "Cy", "answers": ["CY"], "question": "Name starts with 'Cy'" },
  { "substring": "Cu", "answers": ["CU"], "question": "Name starts with 'Cu'" },
  { "substring": "Sy", "answers": ["SY"], "question": "Name starts with 'Sy'" },
  { "substring": "Ky", "answers": ["KG"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ky'" },
  { "substring": "Ke", "answers": ["KE"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ke'" },
  { "substring": "Ki", "answers": ["KI"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ki'" },
  { "substring": "Ku", "answers": ["KW"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ku'" },
  { "substring": "Ka", "answers": ["KZ"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ka'" },
  { "substring": "Dj", "answers": ["DJ"], "question": "Name starts with 'Dj'" },
  { "substring": "Ye", "answers": ["YE"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ye'" },
  { "substring": "Ur", "answers": ["UY"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ur'" },
  { "substring": "Tr", "answers": ["TT"], "question": "Name starts with 'Tr'" },
  { "substring": "Sr", "answers": ["LK"], "question": "Name starts with 'Sr'" },
  { "substring": "Lu", "answers": ["LU"], "question": "Name starts with 'Lu'" },
  { "substring": "Th", "answers": ["TH"], "question": "Name starts with 'Th'" },
  { "substring": "Af", "answers": ["AF"], "question": "Name starts with 'Af'" },
  { "substring": "Ic", "answers": ["IS"], "question": "Name starts with 'Ic'" },
  { "substring": "Az", "answers": ["AZ"], "question": "Name starts with 'Az'" },
  { "substring": "Uk", "answers": ["UA"], "question": "Name starts with 'Uk'" },
  { "substring": "Qa", "answers": ["QA"], "question": "Name starts with 'Qa'" }
]
